Bill Bahlman Papers GLBTQ.1998.01
GLBTQ Archives
- Program for the Hearing on Prevention and Education, Presidential Commission on the Human Immunodeficiency Virus Epidemic, March, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- "Voters organized in coalition for the election”, flyer giving dates and locations of demonstrations, Gay & Lesbian 'VOICE 88', n.d. (Box 1, Folder 106)
- a) "AIDS estimates drop sharply", article by Richard Dunne with side notes handwritten, n.d. b) "Playing games with AIDS stats”, article from the New York Post, November, as flyer asking people to "’Voice your response to Pat Buchanan’ and call the Tribune Media Services at the number given”, n.d. c) " Health chief and AIDS: A chant of critics amid praise", reprint of news article, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 107)
- a) " Quayle embraces patriotic themes and attacks Dukakis on pledge", reprint New York Times, September, 1988 b) "Taking liberty with Dan”, reprint Daily News, September, 1988 c) "Quayle takes liberty route", reprint New York Newsday, September, 1988 d) "Quayle's record in Senate reflects fervently held conservative views", reprint New York Times, August, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 108)
- a) "George Bush has lied to you 10 times!", flyer, New York State Democratic Victory Team, n.d. b) "He's lying", flyer printed by ACT UP (Silence=Death), criticizing Mike Dukakis' stand on AIDS, n.d. c) "Defending lesbian and gay rights", issue brief printed by the Jesse Jackson, '88 campaign office in Chicago, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 109)
- "Election '88 Sub-Committee: Presidential candidates' evaluations”, printed by ACT UP, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 110)
- “Senate hearing concerning amendment no. 956 to prohibit the use of any funds provided under this act to the Centers For Disease Control from being used to provide AIDS education, information, or prevention materials and activities that promote, encourage, or condone homosexual activities”, reprinted form the Congressional Record, Senate, S14202, (changed to amendment # 963) October 14, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 111)
- "Responding to the AIDS crisis", keynote address by Dick Gephardt, National Nurses’ Week, Texas Medical Center, Houston, May, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 112)
- a) "Mothers plan GOP AIDS pitch", reprint San Francisco Examiner, August, 1988 b) “NGLTF, National Gay & Lesbian Task Force”, information sheet telling background of the organization and its purpose, n.d. c) "Read my lips”, flyer announcing a "kiss-In", sponsored by ACT UP, August, 1988 d) "’Die-In’, in memory of all those who have died of AIDS while our government dragged its feet in a 'business as usual' approach”, flyer announcing demonstration at New Orleans City Hall, sponsored by March On, a Los Angeles Activist Group, n.d. e) Information on transportation and restaurants in New Orleans, n.d. f) Map of New Orleans g) Calendar of events for gay/lesbian community's return to Washington during October anniversary of march, n.d. h) Statement from Gay and Lesbian Voice '88 on Republican Party Draft Platform, 1987 i) Calendar of events at Republican convention, New Orleans, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 113)
- a) Personal letter to Dr. William Bahlman, from Louis Plattner, Washington, D.C., November 11, 1987 b) Washington National Airport taxicab information, n.d. c) Hotel brochures, n.d. d) Shuttle bus schedule for the I.C.A.A.C. '87 conference for the American Society for Microbiology, 1987 e) List of services, stores, restaurants, etc. available to the gay & lesbian community, reprinted from the Gayellow Pages, n.d. f) Copies of maps of Washington D.C. and New York City, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 114)
- a) "Gays arrested in protest against Catholic Church", "Bishops approve condom information; O’Connor dissents", "Michigan bookstore battles vandalism, local homophobes”, reprints, The Advocate, January, 1989 b) “CDC AIDS Conference” by Dave Walter, reprint, The Advocate, March, 1987 c) "The new gay activism: Adding bite to the movement", reprint, The Advocate, June, 1988 d) " News threats prompt new tactics in California", reprint, The Advocate, February, 1988 e) “Mood Indigo: Singing the blues at the Republicans' New Orleans Convention", The Advocate, September, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 115)
- ACT UP New York: An ACT UP chronology, March 1987-May 1994 (Box 1, Folder 116)